{
    "question": "Contoh soal soal persuading",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Why don\u2019t you\ntry our special drink bandrek to warm up your body?\n\n\n\n\n<br><span>\nIf I were you, I\nwould \u2026 ?</span>\n<span>\n\u00a0I\u2019m sure you are\non the right track.?</span>\n\n\n<br><span>\n\u00a0<span>I bet you could\ndo it.?</span></span><br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-spoof-pake-twist-falling-into-a-well-dong-306",
            "question": "Contoh text SPOOF pake twist \"falling into a well\" dong :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nSpoof text: Falling Into a Well</span>\n<span>\n</span>\n\nThere was a man. When he was walking, he fell into a well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nMany people saw the incident so they came to save him. Unfortunately no \none could enter the well to bring him out. Later, a smart man came up \nwith a bright idea to throw the man a strong rope to try to pull him out\n the well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nWhen the rope reached\u00a0 and hit the man\u2019s head, he shouted angrily: \u201cDon&#039; bother me! Pick your own well, I am bathing.\u201d\n<br>\n\nDo you get the point why that short passage can be labeled as a spoof \ntext? Before we are going to go further, Let&#039;s see its rough translation\n to help you to\u00a0 get better understanding\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858",
            "question": "Whats is the problem from the story \"Snow Bride\"",
            "attachments": [
                "question-attachments/whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858-1.docx"
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Carilah kata-kata yang terdengar janggal dan aneh... :)Mandiri lebih baik.<br>Okay ? @Liwed",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-contoh-berita-acara-serah-terima-pekerjaan-proyek-558",
            "question": "Ada yang tau contoh Berita Acara Serah Terima Pekerjaan (Proyek) dalam bahasa Inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><em>Handover Works (Project</em><span><em>)</em></span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buatin-dialog-expresing-anger-untuk-2-orang-524",
            "question": "Tolong buatin dialog expresing anger :)\r\nuntuk 2 orang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Everyone Has Bad Day<br>Sari\t: Hey, Rangga!<br> Rangga\t: What displeasure!<br> Sari\t: What? What happened, Rangga? Are you angry about something?<br> Rangga\t: Oh, I\u2019m very sorry, Sari. I was walking near handkerchief. You can wipe up your wet shirt.<br>Rangga\t: Oh, thank you, Sari. So, how was your day, Sari? Did something bad happen to you too? Haha I\u2019m kidding, Sari.<br> Sari\t: Actually, something bad did happen to me. It\u2019s still driving me mad until now.<br> Rangga\t: Oh, really? What do you look so insulted about?<br>\n Sari\t: It\u2019s my boss. He said that I can have a day-offs earlier but \ntoday he revoked what he said. I was planning on going for a vacation on\n my day-offs with my family. I am extremely displeased about that.<br> Rangga\t: I\u2019m sorry to hear that.<br> Sari\t: Well, everyone has bad day but if we still consider it positively, everything is going to be alright<br> Rangga\t: Yeah, I think you\u2019re right<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "A = <span>why are you scared?<br>B = i&#039;am sorry. i spoil your diary.<br>A = what?? why did you do that?<br>B = i didn&#039;t purposely. sorry<br>A = wether the sorry can repair all?<br>B = OK. i will replace your diary, but iam sorry<br>A = it&#039;s up to you. <br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantuin-aku-dong-cari-biografi-aknes-monica-menggunakan-bahasa-in-292",
            "question": "Bantuin aku dong cari Biografi aknes monica menggunakan Bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Agnes Monica Muljoto. Born in Jakarta 1 July 1986, known abroad as Agnes Mo. She stared her career in the entertainment industry at the age of six as a child singer. She jobs is singer, actress, dancer, voice actress, and producer.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-perbedaan-antara-simple-past-tense-dengan-present-perfect-ten-100",
            "question": "Apa perbedaan antara simple past tense dengan present perfect tense ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple pastanse untuk menyatakan kejadian yang sudah lalu<br>present perfect untuk menyatakan kejadian yang direncanakan",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "simple past tense dipakai saat keterangan waktunya sudah selesai, \nsedangkan present perfect dipakai saat keterangan waktunya belum \nselesai/masih berlanjut.<br>Contoh:<br>I bought 3 books last week. (simple past-last week sudah berlalu)<br>I have bought 3 books this week. (present perfect-this week belum berlalu, masih berlangsung)<br><br>present perfect menggunakan &#039;for&#039; dan &#039;since&#039; saat kegiatannya masih berlanjut.<br><br>I have lived in London for 3 years. (present perfect-masih berlangsung, sekarang pun masih di London)<br>I have lived in London since 1990. (sampai sekarang masih tinggal di London)\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "narrative-text-yang-bagus-dan-jarang-di-dengar-orang-797",
            "question": "Narrative text yang bagus dan jarang di dengar orang??",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The story snow white<br>In earlier times there lived a , who named Snow White . He lived with his aunt and uncle because his parents died . One day she heard her uncle and aunt talking about leaving Snow White in the castle because they wanted to go to America and they did not have enough money to take Snow White with them . princess Snow White did not want her uncle and aunt to do this . So he decided to escape .<br><br><span>\u00a0The next day he ran away from home when her aunt and uncle were having breakfast , he fled into the wood . In the wood she felt very tired and hungry . Then she saw this cottage . She knocked but no one answered her so she went inside and felt asleep Meanwhile seven dwarfs came home from his work . They get into . There, they found Snow White woke up from his sleep . He saw the dwarfs . The dwarf said : \" What is your name ? &#039; Snow White said , \" My name is Snow White . \" One dwarf said , \" If you want , you can stay here with us . &#039; Snow White tells all about her story . Then daughter snow and the seven dwarves are now living happily ever after .</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-386",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "My beloved home<br><br>It is located in the central park. My home is the sweetest home on my complex. It has green roof which is made from special clay. Therefore it is always shining when the sun light rise in the morning.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-the-word-darling-is-derived-from-an-old-english-term-meaning-251",
            "question": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old english term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".    2. IBM is has laid of 20 percent of their workforce with a signature on a single piece of paper.\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6\r\na. Find out the error option.\r\nb. Explain why it is wrong\r\n\r\nmohon bantuannya yaa..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old English term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".<br>Positive Meaning : It&#039;s a person that we concern as lovely and lovable, therefore we prioritize this darling as the first priority.<br>Negative : Since the word darling means favorite minion, it also trigger the feeling of possessiveness, that sometime it has negative effect on their freedom and privacy.\u00a0<br><br><span>2.\u00a0</span><u>IBM</u><span>\u00a0is\u00a0</span><u>has</u><span>\u00a0laid of\u00a0</span><u>20 percent</u><span>\u00a0of\u00a0</span><u>their</u>\u00a0<u>workforce</u><span>\u00a0with a signature on a\u00a0</span><u>single</u><span>\u00a0piece of paper.</span><br>\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6<br>a. Find out the error option.<br><br>number 2 - &gt; should be<br>IBM has laid without &#039;is&#039;\u00a0<br>b. Explain why it is wrong<br>if we use Is, then it will have pasive meaning, which means that IBM get bankrupt due to their worker\u00a0<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}